Hi, we are here in Shinjuku, Tokyo.
Today, we're going to visit a cat cafe🐈💓
The cat cafe we're visiting today is just a 2-minute walk from Shinjuku Station.
We'll head down Shinjuku Central Street.
It's on the 6th floor of that building. The location is a bit tricky to find, so be careful⚠️
It's 3 p.m. now. We plan to have plenty of fun at the cat cafe until the evening.
This time, We'll also show you a little bit of what the cats are like when the cafe closes☺️
This is the front desk.
You check in with a tablet.
You can choose from Japanese, English, Chinese, or Korean.
You pay when you leave, the machine will calculate your total based on how long you stayed.
This is the slipper machine.
>> Staff: Please change into slippers.
>> Staff: There are lockers in the back. Please leave your shoes and belongings there.
The locker room is quite spacious.
If you have large luggage like suitcases, you can leave them at the front desk.
Once you've chosen a locker and put your belongings in, lock it🔑
On the key, there are rules written like "Please do not use flash photography". Let's make sure to check them.
There are clean washrooms and two restrooms near the locker room.
Drinks are all you can drink.
They have a wide variety of drinks like juice, cocoa, coffee, and more🥤✨
"The recommendation this month is Maple Tea"
Remember to put a lid on your cup so it doesn't get knocked over by a cat.
These are the cats that are here. They're all too cute.
Let's go meet them.
The cat space has a door.
It has a stylish atmosphere, doesn't it?
Cat Cafe Mocha is a chain store with branches all over the country, but the Shinjuku branch is one of the largest.
Please note that this branch is only for guests 13 years and older.
It's spacious yet intricate design allows you to enjoy your time without worrying about other guests.
Weekday rates are 220 yen (1.58 USD / € 1.47) for every 10 minutes. The maximum charge is 2,640 yen (19.00 USD / € 17.65).
There's an additional charge of 385 yen (2.77 USD / € 2.57) for the drinks.
If you stay for more than 2 hours, the maximum charge is applied automatically.
Oops, sorry😭 I surprised you there.
They have a wide variety of manga! They even have the latest titles.
In the back, there's a space with larger tables and sofas.
The cafe is very clean, and there's no smell at all.
Hello there.
There are beds where you can lie down with cats, your partner, or your friends.
The staff are always taking care of the cats and cleaning the room.
This is Kinu-Kun, getting his nails clipped.
He's looking pretty unhappy (Ｕ˘•_•˘Ｕ) I'm sorry but so cute. haha
Good job for being so calm.
There are small doors leading to the staff room scattered about, and you can see the cats going in and out every now and then👀
That's where the the cat's litter boxes are.
There are water stations in the cafe space.
After the cats' breakfast time, there's apparently a line for this water station.
Many cats are curious about the camera and often come closer on their own.
Blanc-Kun is very interested.
You are allowed to touch the cats at the cafe. Gently pet them☺️
The cats are cute and unique, and they're very healing haha
There's a lot of facilities, so there are many people who come here alone or use it for work or study.
They lend out chargers and have outlets and free Wi-Fi.
There are blankets available too.
You can try the crane game for free twice per person.
Let's give it a shot.
Oh, I did it!
Remember, the snacks inside the capsules are for humans, not cats.
I got Cuppy Ramune.
Here is the capsule toy for cat snacks.
Laki-Kun is staring at us.
Wow, I got a cat punch!
Hey, hey 😂
Petite snack: 100 yen (0.72 USD / € 0.67)
Be careful, as only 100 yen coins can be used. Make sure to bring cash!
Hmm? I feel a gaze...
In addition to these snacks, they also sell cat ice cream, cat manma, and cat cocktails for 550 yen (3.96 USD / € 3.67).
There's also a "Nyan Nyan Set" for 1,100 yen (7.91 USD / € 7.35) where you can take a picture holding a cat of your choice and cat ice cream.
The set is only sold at the Shinjuku store🐈
It gets busy around 3 to 6 pm, so there are some cats who aren't hungry.
Any cats want a snack?
Anzu-Chan came over🥺
Ume-Chan came too. Do you want to eat?
Here you go.
You don't want it?!
Is it good?☺️
Ume-Chan keeps coming over to tease.
What's with that sitting position?😂
It's amusing and cute with lots of charm.
Do you want to eat too, Komachi-Chan?
Your round and sparkling eyes are so cute.
Oh, she ate it.
At first, you seemed a bit surprised, but I think you're already friends with the camera.
So fluffy
ASMR cat chewing near the microphone.
To get along with the cats, treats are a must.
When you go to a cat cafe, be sure to give them some snacks☺️
A space where you can stretch out and relax.
The floor is Japanese tatami, so you take off your slippers.
Thanks for showing us around.
Here you can enjoy card games and board games for free. There's a lot of variety!
The fact that humans can also enjoy their own time freely is a charm of MOCHA.
Let's try out the TV game space.
We played Super Smash Bros on the Nintendo Switch.
Have you ever played it?
There are also toys for the cats.
I wonder if anyone will come over😚
Wow, an unexpected Ninja Stella-Chan came from somewhere.
Haru-Chan is a kitten born in October 2022.
Depending on the mood of the cat, kittens are more likely to play with you than adult cats.
The Shinjuku branch has quite a few kittens. They're tiny, curious, and super cute.
Anzu-Chan in sleepy mode.
She's taken over the borrowed charger case completely.
Oh, Kurage-Chan spotted the camera.
She's a girl born in October 2022. She's very curious.
She bit it! haha
It's cute, so you can forgive anything.
Cat ice cream: 550 yen (3.96 USD / € 3.67)
Komachi-Chan, want some?
You don't want it?
You don't seem to be in the mood either.
Tamae-Chan ate it.
She's adorable eating earnestly with a stern face.
So cute that we are smitten🐱
How about Soboro-Chan?
This cat ice cream is a type of liquid cat treat that has been frozen.
I wonder if they're not cold? But once they start eating, everyone gets hooked😂
She really eat it deliciously.
Somehow it's cute like a tiger.
💓
She's tilting her head a lot. LOL, so cute🤭
It was good, wasn't it?
Thank you for eating all of it.
Now, let's get some work done.
The Wi-Fi download speed is 230Mbps. It's fast and comfortable.
What's up, Stella-Chan?
Being cheered on by cats while working or studying is too blissful.
Especially this table has lots of outlets, so you can work for a long time.
Drinks are also all-you-can-drink, so it seems like it would be more productive than going to a regular cafe. haha
That's your favorite place. Thanks for being with us.
A staff member came over.
When a staff member comes, all the cats suddenly become very affectionate, which is very cute🥺
Stella-Chan can do tricks! We were taught how to do it.
Amazing! How cute!!
>> Staff: Good girl.
Will she do it for me too?
Ah, she ate the snack. Failure.
Wow, what a gentle and good girl. Thank you, Stella-Chan.
Normally you pay afterwards, but you can pay the maximum fee in advance and go out in between.
Let's go eat dinner.
Since it's Shinjuku, there are plenty of restaurants, but today we feel like ramen🍜
We came to Yokohama-style ramen shop, just a minute walk from the cat cafe.
Yokohama-style ramen, salt, large: 1,000 yen (7.19 USD / € 6.68)
Yokohama-style ramen, soy sauce: 880 yen (6.33 USD / € 5.88)
I love ramen.
The noodles were thick and rich, and it was delicious! Thank you for the meal.
We are back
Here comes the fluffy one.
After 7 PM, the number of customers in the cafe started to decrease.
Relaxed mode Ram-Chan. She's chubby and cute.
From 7:30 PM, it's dinner time for the cats.
As feeding time approaches, the cats start to get restless and seem to become more active than in the afternoon💭
It's interesting and cute just watching the communication between the cats🤣
The chubby flesh around his neck is cute.
Thanks for the service shot.
Now it's almost dinner time for the cats. They're all gathered because they're hungry.
At MOCHA, there are two feeding times for the cats, at 10:30 am and 7:30 pm.
It's recommended to visit at this time to see their very cute appearance.
Oh, it seems like dinner time is about to start.
>> Staff: We will now start the cats' dinner time.
>> Staff: The cats eat in a line on the round stage, so please watch from the other side.
Everyone's tail wagging is cute.
>> Staff: Now, let's start lining up the cat's meals.
This is indeed a spectacular view.
The sight of them lined up and eating eagerly is really cute.
The cats who have finished eating are leaving.
Who's the biggest foodie today?
When the staff holds it, I wonder if it looks delicious.
The turnover of the finalists is intense.
I'm starting to lose track of who will win.
>> Staff: That's it for dinner time. Thank you very much.
The winner is Ram? Raisin? They're twins, so I don't know which one!😂
The closing time is 8 PM. Today we are going to show you what it's like at closing time.
After closing, the cats also go home.
>> Staff: Please take a close-up. This is Daiya-Kun.
There are many cats who don't want to go home, and this is actually the most hard job.
>> Staff: Bye-bye.
>> Staff: Ayame-chan, you should say bye-bye too. Where's your hand?
After closing, they clean the cafe, arrange supplies, check the cats' health, and so on.
>> Staff: Aren't you going to run away? Good girl.
When the staff handles them, they all become like babies and it's really cute...👶
>> Staff: I'm leaving!
Take care on your way home.
>> Staff: Hey, Kanro.
>> Staff: It's time to go home.
>> Staff: He is big and heavy.
>> Staff: He's angry.
Some cats don't want to go home so much that they play hide and seek with the staff.
>> Staff: Gotcha!
>> Staff: You ran quite a bit, didn't you?
It was really a fun day. Thank you for watching!